{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479589564","data":{"timestamp":" 947479589564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mama_bibi-mwanafunzi-mama"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" bibi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479595493","data":{"timestamp":" 947479595492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mama_bibi-mwanafunzi-mama"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" mama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479601268","data":{"timestamp":" 947479601268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_babu_mwalimu-kinyozi-babu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" babu"," userResponse":" kinyozi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479607929","data":{"timestamp":" 947479607929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_babu_mwalimu-kinyozi-babu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" babu"," userResponse":" babu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479613568","data":{"timestamp":" 947479613568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mjoma_dada-kinyozi-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mjoma"," userResponse":" dada"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479619487","data":{"timestamp":" 947479619487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mjoma_dada-kinyozi-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mjoma"," userResponse":" kinyozi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479625663","data":{"timestamp":" 947479625663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mjoma_dada-kinyozi-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mjoma"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479630986","data":{"timestamp":" 947479630985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_baba_kaka-baba-mama"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" mama"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479636702","data":{"timestamp":" 947479636701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_baba_kaka-baba-mama"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" kaka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479642095","data":{"timestamp":" 947479642095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_baba_kaka-baba-mama"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479648678","data":{"timestamp":" 947479648678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shangazi_shangazi-bibi-dada"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shangazi"," userResponse":" dada"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479655245","data":{"timestamp":" 947479655245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shangazi_shangazi-bibi-dada"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shangazi"," userResponse":" shangazi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479661422","data":{"timestamp":" 947479661422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kinyozi_babu-shangazi-kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kinyozi"," userResponse":" shangazi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479668252","data":{"timestamp":" 947479668252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kinyozi_babu-shangazi-kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kinyozi"," userResponse":" kinyozi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479673192","data":{"timestamp":" 947479673192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mkulima_mkulima-mwanafunzi-bibi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mkulima"," userResponse":" mkulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479678686","data":{"timestamp":" 947479678686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwanafunzi_kinyozi-mwanafunzi-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" kinyozi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479685611","data":{"timestamp":" 947479685611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwanafunzi_kinyozi-mwanafunzi-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwalimu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479692137","data":{"timestamp":" 947479692137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwanafunzi_kinyozi-mwanafunzi-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479704132","data":{"timestamp":" 947479704132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwalimu_mkulima-kinyozi-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwalimu"," userResponse":" mwalimu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479717260","data":{"timestamp":" 947479717260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_dada_baba-mjoma-dada"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dada"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479723019","data":{"timestamp":" 947479723019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_dada_baba-mjoma-dada"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dada"," userResponse":" dada"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479728775","data":{"timestamp":" 947479728775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8637421b-e591-468d-8064-1dd58e1548fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_dada_baba-mjoma-dada"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479743808","data":{"timestamp":" 947479743808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 436c2b7c-029a-4844-a003-2744d636afba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479786644","data":{"timestamp":" 947479786643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 436c2b7c-029a-4844-a003-2744d636afba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479786731","data":{"timestamp":" 947479786731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 436c2b7c-029a-4844-a003-2744d636afba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479831681","data":{"timestamp":" 947479831680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 436c2b7c-029a-4844-a003-2744d636afba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479853101","data":{"timestamp":" 947479853101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 0a8c872c-1ce3-4611-9d84-7620f55c00da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mkulima_babu-bibi-mkulima"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mkulima"," userResponse":" mkulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479860250","data":{"timestamp":" 947479860250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 0a8c872c-1ce3-4611-9d84-7620f55c00da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_baba_baba-dada-shangazi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" dada"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479866025","data":{"timestamp":" 947479866025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 0a8c872c-1ce3-4611-9d84-7620f55c00da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_baba_baba-dada-shangazi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479873379","data":{"timestamp":" 947479873379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 0a8c872c-1ce3-4611-9d84-7620f55c00da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_dada_dada-mkulima-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dada"," userResponse":" dada"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479882410","data":{"timestamp":" 947479882410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 0a8c872c-1ce3-4611-9d84-7620f55c00da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwanafunzi_mwanafunzi-mama-shangazi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479888043","data":{"timestamp":" 947479888043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 0a8c872c-1ce3-4611-9d84-7620f55c00da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kinyozi_mkulima-kinyozi-bibi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kinyozi"," userResponse":" mkulima"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479895598","data":{"timestamp":" 947479895598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 0a8c872c-1ce3-4611-9d84-7620f55c00da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kinyozi_mkulima-kinyozi-bibi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kinyozi"," userResponse":" kinyozi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479900346","data":{"timestamp":" 947479900346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 0a8c872c-1ce3-4611-9d84-7620f55c00da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kaka_dada-mwanafunzi-kaka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kaka"," userResponse":" dada"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479906164","data":{"timestamp":" 947479906163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 0a8c872c-1ce3-4611-9d84-7620f55c00da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kaka_dada-mwanafunzi-kaka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kaka"," userResponse":" kaka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479913023","data":{"timestamp":" 947479913022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 0a8c872c-1ce3-4611-9d84-7620f55c00da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwalimu_mjoma-mwalimu-shangazi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwalimu"," userResponse":" shangazi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479920084","data":{"timestamp":" 947479920084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 0a8c872c-1ce3-4611-9d84-7620f55c00da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwalimu_mjoma-mwalimu-shangazi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwalimu"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479925938","data":{"timestamp":" 947479925938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 0a8c872c-1ce3-4611-9d84-7620f55c00da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwalimu_mjoma-mwalimu-shangazi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwalimu"," userResponse":" mwalimu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479930828","data":{"timestamp":" 947479930828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 0a8c872c-1ce3-4611-9d84-7620f55c00da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_babu_babu-mama-bibi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" babu"," userResponse":" babu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479938378","data":{"timestamp":" 947479938378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 0a8c872c-1ce3-4611-9d84-7620f55c00da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bibi_mwanafunzi-dada-bibi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bibi"," userResponse":" bibi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479950811","data":{"timestamp":" 947479950811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 0a8c872c-1ce3-4611-9d84-7620f55c00da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mjoma_baba-kaka-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mjoma"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947479956601","data":{"timestamp":" 947479956599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 0a8c872c-1ce3-4611-9d84-7620f55c00da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mjoma_baba-kaka-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480011825","data":{"timestamp":" 947480011825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" df5e294c-865f-4183-9304-6bf4144e1903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kinyozi_mkulima-kinyozi-bibi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kinyozi"," userResponse":" kinyozi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480025543","data":{"timestamp":" 947480025543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" df5e294c-865f-4183-9304-6bf4144e1903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_babu_babu-mama-bibi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" babu"," userResponse":" babu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480038630","data":{"timestamp":" 947480038630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" df5e294c-865f-4183-9304-6bf4144e1903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_baba_baba-dada-shangazi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" dada"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480047043","data":{"timestamp":" 947480047043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" df5e294c-865f-4183-9304-6bf4144e1903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_baba_baba-dada-shangazi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480052652","data":{"timestamp":" 947480052652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" df5e294c-865f-4183-9304-6bf4144e1903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kaka_dada-mwanafunzi-kaka"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kaka"," userResponse":" kaka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480059208","data":{"timestamp":" 947480059208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" df5e294c-865f-4183-9304-6bf4144e1903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mjoma_baba-kaka-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mjoma"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480064459","data":{"timestamp":" 947480064459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" df5e294c-865f-4183-9304-6bf4144e1903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwalimu_mjoma-mwalimu-shangazi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwalimu"," userResponse":" mwalimu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480070214","data":{"timestamp":" 947480070214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" df5e294c-865f-4183-9304-6bf4144e1903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bibi_mwanafunzi-dada-bibi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bibi"," userResponse":" bibi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480076062","data":{"timestamp":" 947480076062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" df5e294c-865f-4183-9304-6bf4144e1903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mkulima_babu-bibi-mkulima"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mkulima"," userResponse":" mkulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480081612","data":{"timestamp":" 947480081612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" df5e294c-865f-4183-9304-6bf4144e1903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwanafunzi_mwanafunzi-mama-shangazi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480086411","data":{"timestamp":" 947480086411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" df5e294c-865f-4183-9304-6bf4144e1903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_dada_dada-mkulima-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dada"," userResponse":" dada"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480092185","data":{"timestamp":" 947480092183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" df5e294c-865f-4183-9304-6bf4144e1903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_dada_dada-mkulima-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480106204","data":{"timestamp":" 947480106204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 7d23b87b-5485-42d0-98a8-cc18e7003f50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480108075","data":{"timestamp":" 947480108075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 7d23b87b-5485-42d0-98a8-cc18e7003f50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480108150","data":{"timestamp":" 947480108150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 7d23b87b-5485-42d0-98a8-cc18e7003f50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480122066","data":{"timestamp":" 947480122066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 7d23b87b-5485-42d0-98a8-cc18e7003f50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.people.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480154334","data":{"timestamp":" 947480154334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 7747891b-aa29-40f4-8949-e6aad7f859d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.people.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_baba_bibi_mjoma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.people.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480160997","data":{"timestamp":" 947480160996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 7747891b-aa29-40f4-8949-e6aad7f859d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.people.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_shangazi_mwanafunzi_dada"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.people.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480167665","data":{"timestamp":" 947480167665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 7747891b-aa29-40f4-8949-e6aad7f859d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.people.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mjoma_mwalimu_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.people.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480174291","data":{"timestamp":" 947480174291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 7747891b-aa29-40f4-8949-e6aad7f859d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.people.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kinyozi_bibi_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.people.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480180917","data":{"timestamp":" 947480180917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 7747891b-aa29-40f4-8949-e6aad7f859d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.people.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_baba_kaka_babu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.people.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480187578","data":{"timestamp":" 947480187578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 7747891b-aa29-40f4-8949-e6aad7f859d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.people.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mwalimu_kaka_mama"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.people.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480194235","data":{"timestamp":" 947480194234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 7747891b-aa29-40f4-8949-e6aad7f859d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.people.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mwalimu_kaka_babu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.people.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480200893","data":{"timestamp":" 947480200893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 7747891b-aa29-40f4-8949-e6aad7f859d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.people.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mjoma_mkulima_shangazi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.people.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480207571","data":{"timestamp":" 947480207571"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 7747891b-aa29-40f4-8949-e6aad7f859d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.people.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kinyozi_bibi_mjoma"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.people.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480214216","data":{"timestamp":" 947480214214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 7747891b-aa29-40f4-8949-e6aad7f859d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.people.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_dada_baba_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.people.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480226304","data":{"timestamp":" 947480226303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 7747891b-aa29-40f4-8949-e6aad7f859d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.people.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_dada_baba_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480239848","data":{"timestamp":" 947480239847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" MKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480243526","data":{"timestamp":" 947480243525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" MKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480245136","data":{"timestamp":" 947480245136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480248080","data":{"timestamp":" 947480248079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480249690","data":{"timestamp":" 947480249690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480252907","data":{"timestamp":" 947480252907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480254520","data":{"timestamp":" 947480254519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOTI"," userResponse":" GOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480257364","data":{"timestamp":" 947480257363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOTI"," userResponse":" GOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480258957","data":{"timestamp":" 947480258956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mdomo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480261699","data":{"timestamp":" 947480261698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mdomo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480263310","data":{"timestamp":" 947480263310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" meno"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480265975","data":{"timestamp":" 947480265975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" meno"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480267583","data":{"timestamp":" 947480267583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480270338","data":{"timestamp":" 947480270337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480271941","data":{"timestamp":" 947480271941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480274688","data":{"timestamp":" 947480274688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480276311","data":{"timestamp":" 947480276310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480284891","data":{"timestamp":" 947480284891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480286518","data":{"timestamp":" 947480286517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480288785","data":{"timestamp":" 947480288784"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480290432","data":{"timestamp":" 947480290430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480292698","data":{"timestamp":" 947480292697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480294299","data":{"timestamp":" 947480294298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480297453","data":{"timestamp":" 947480297452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480299113","data":{"timestamp":" 947480299112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" NYAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480303338","data":{"timestamp":" 947480303337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" NYAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480305367","data":{"timestamp":" 947480305366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480305498","data":{"timestamp":" 947480305498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 312d78df-1308-4153-b886-d38bf8d66930"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-body.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" NYAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480320978","data":{"timestamp":" 947480320977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOTI"," userResponse":" GOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480324850","data":{"timestamp":" 947480324850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOTI"," userResponse":" GOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480326454","data":{"timestamp":" 947480326453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480331586","data":{"timestamp":" 947480331586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480333188","data":{"timestamp":" 947480333187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mdomo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480337572","data":{"timestamp":" 947480337572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mdomo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480339172","data":{"timestamp":" 947480339172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480341710","data":{"timestamp":" 947480341710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480343310","data":{"timestamp":" 947480343309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" meno"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480350647","data":{"timestamp":" 947480350646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" meno"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480352274","data":{"timestamp":" 947480352273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" MKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480354860","data":{"timestamp":" 947480354860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" MKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480356478","data":{"timestamp":" 947480356477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" NYAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480363676","data":{"timestamp":" 947480363675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" NYAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480365308","data":{"timestamp":" 947480365307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480368197","data":{"timestamp":" 947480368196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480369825","data":{"timestamp":" 947480369825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480376997","data":{"timestamp":" 947480376996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480378608","data":{"timestamp":" 947480378607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480390999","data":{"timestamp":" 947480390999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480392609","data":{"timestamp":" 947480392608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480405732","data":{"timestamp":" 947480405732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480407338","data":{"timestamp":" 947480407337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480411002","data":{"timestamp":" 947480411001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480412625","data":{"timestamp":" 947480412625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480415201","data":{"timestamp":" 947480415200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480417232","data":{"timestamp":" 947480417230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480417349","data":{"timestamp":" 947480417349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 2d7fc3ab-f813-43d3-9b85-d1370ddb2f61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480431737","data":{"timestamp":" 947480431737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480432805","data":{"timestamp":" 947480432804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vidole"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480439402","data":{"timestamp":" 947480439402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480440471","data":{"timestamp":" 947480440470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480444672","data":{"timestamp":" 947480444671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480445732","data":{"timestamp":" 947480445731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480449789","data":{"timestamp":" 947480449788"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480450853","data":{"timestamp":" 947480450852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480454459","data":{"timestamp":" 947480454459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" START_MKONO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480455289","data":{"timestamp":" 947480455289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" MKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480456352","data":{"timestamp":" 947480456352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" MKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480460551","data":{"timestamp":" 947480460551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480461604","data":{"timestamp":" 947480461604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480465611","data":{"timestamp":" 947480465611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480466672","data":{"timestamp":" 947480466671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480470609","data":{"timestamp":" 947480470608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mdomo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480471675","data":{"timestamp":" 947480471674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mdomo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480475679","data":{"timestamp":" 947480475678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480476743","data":{"timestamp":" 947480476742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480480356","data":{"timestamp":" 947480480355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480481422","data":{"timestamp":" 947480481421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480485653","data":{"timestamp":" 947480485652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOTI"," userResponse":" GOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480486724","data":{"timestamp":" 947480486724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOTI"," userResponse":" GOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480489887","data":{"timestamp":" 947480489886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" NYAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480490978","data":{"timestamp":" 947480490977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" NYAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480494105","data":{"timestamp":" 947480494105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" meno"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480495175","data":{"timestamp":" 947480495174"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" meno"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480498898","data":{"timestamp":" 947480498897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" meno"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480499014","data":{"timestamp":" 947480499014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" b58ad7cd-b4cc-4fab-a8c0-53a65b8e76ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" meno"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480512111","data":{"timestamp":" 947480512111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 59c31005-1640-413c-890e-521ca7cd869d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_goti_mguu-goti-vidole"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" goti"," userResponse":" goti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480518001","data":{"timestamp":" 947480518001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 59c31005-1640-413c-890e-521ca7cd869d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mguu_mguu-bega-meno"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mguu"," userResponse":" bega"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480524450","data":{"timestamp":" 947480524450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 59c31005-1640-413c-890e-521ca7cd869d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mguu_mguu-bega-meno"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mguu"," userResponse":" mguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480530221","data":{"timestamp":" 947480530221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 59c31005-1640-413c-890e-521ca7cd869d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_meno_mdomo-meno-jicho"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" meno"," userResponse":" meno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480543843","data":{"timestamp":" 947480543843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 59c31005-1640-413c-890e-521ca7cd869d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyayo_nyayo-vidole-tumbo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyayo"," userResponse":" nyayo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480549300","data":{"timestamp":" 947480549300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 59c31005-1640-413c-890e-521ca7cd869d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kichwa_vidole-kichwa-pua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kichwa"," userResponse":" kichwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480554363","data":{"timestamp":" 947480554362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 59c31005-1640-413c-890e-521ca7cd869d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jicho_jicho-mdomo-mkono"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jicho"," userResponse":" jicho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480559384","data":{"timestamp":" 947480559384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 59c31005-1640-413c-890e-521ca7cd869d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mkono_tumbo-mkono-mdomo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mkono"," userResponse":" mkono"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480565965","data":{"timestamp":" 947480565965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 59c31005-1640-413c-890e-521ca7cd869d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bega_mguu-nyayo-bega"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bega"," userResponse":" bega"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480571685","data":{"timestamp":" 947480571685"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 59c31005-1640-413c-890e-521ca7cd869d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tumbo_tumbo-bega-mguu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tumbo"," userResponse":" mguu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480578443","data":{"timestamp":" 947480578443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 59c31005-1640-413c-890e-521ca7cd869d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tumbo_tumbo-bega-mguu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tumbo"," userResponse":" tumbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480584035","data":{"timestamp":" 947480584035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 59c31005-1640-413c-890e-521ca7cd869d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pua_pua-bega-mguu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pua"," userResponse":" pua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480589807","data":{"timestamp":" 947480589807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 59c31005-1640-413c-890e-521ca7cd869d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_pua_pua-bega-mguu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480604660","data":{"timestamp":" 947480604660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 03507f44-aa95-47f4-bfc4-df5b3c151ec0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mguu_meno-goti-mguu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mguu"," userResponse":" mguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480615983","data":{"timestamp":" 947480615983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 03507f44-aa95-47f4-bfc4-df5b3c151ec0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vidole_nyayo-mdomo-vidole"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vidole"," userResponse":" vidole"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480621583","data":{"timestamp":" 947480621582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 03507f44-aa95-47f4-bfc4-df5b3c151ec0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_goti_pua-nyayo-goti"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" goti"," userResponse":" goti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480627053","data":{"timestamp":" 947480627053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 03507f44-aa95-47f4-bfc4-df5b3c151ec0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_meno_vidole-nyayo-meno"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" meno"," userResponse":" meno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480634043","data":{"timestamp":" 947480634043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 03507f44-aa95-47f4-bfc4-df5b3c151ec0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pua_pua-jicho-tumbo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pua"," userResponse":" pua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480639668","data":{"timestamp":" 947480639668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 03507f44-aa95-47f4-bfc4-df5b3c151ec0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kichwa_bega-kichwa-meno"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kichwa"," userResponse":" kichwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480646068","data":{"timestamp":" 947480646068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 03507f44-aa95-47f4-bfc4-df5b3c151ec0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sikio_mkono-sikio-mdomo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sikio"," userResponse":" sikio"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480653220","data":{"timestamp":" 947480653220"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 03507f44-aa95-47f4-bfc4-df5b3c151ec0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mkono_nyayo-mkono-vidole"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mkono"," userResponse":" mkono"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480666270","data":{"timestamp":" 947480666270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 03507f44-aa95-47f4-bfc4-df5b3c151ec0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tumbo_tumbo-sikio-mkono"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tumbo"," userResponse":" tumbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480681301","data":{"timestamp":" 947480681301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 03507f44-aa95-47f4-bfc4-df5b3c151ec0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jicho_kichwa-jicho-mguu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jicho"," userResponse":" kichwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480688190","data":{"timestamp":" 947480688190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 03507f44-aa95-47f4-bfc4-df5b3c151ec0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jicho_kichwa-jicho-mguu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jicho"," userResponse":" jicho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480693980","data":{"timestamp":" 947480693979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 03507f44-aa95-47f4-bfc4-df5b3c151ec0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.body.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_jicho_kichwa-jicho-mguu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.body.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480734266","data":{"timestamp":" 947480734266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8a1d9992-9d13-45fe-89fe-3ba07140ad8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.body.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_bega_jicho_tumbo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.body.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480740921","data":{"timestamp":" 947480740921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8a1d9992-9d13-45fe-89fe-3ba07140ad8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.body.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mdomo_meno_nyayo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.body.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480747533","data":{"timestamp":" 947480747532"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8a1d9992-9d13-45fe-89fe-3ba07140ad8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.body.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pua_mdomo_vidole"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.body.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480754171","data":{"timestamp":" 947480754171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8a1d9992-9d13-45fe-89fe-3ba07140ad8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.body.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vidole_nyayo_sikio"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.body.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480760786","data":{"timestamp":" 947480760786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8a1d9992-9d13-45fe-89fe-3ba07140ad8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.body.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sikio_jicho_vidole"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.body.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480768278","data":{"timestamp":" 947480768278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8a1d9992-9d13-45fe-89fe-3ba07140ad8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.body.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sikio_jicho_vidole"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.body.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480774936","data":{"timestamp":" 947480774936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8a1d9992-9d13-45fe-89fe-3ba07140ad8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.body.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mdomo_vidole_nyayo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.body.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480781592","data":{"timestamp":" 947480781592"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8a1d9992-9d13-45fe-89fe-3ba07140ad8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.body.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kichwa_jicho_mguu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.body.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480788220","data":{"timestamp":" 947480788219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8a1d9992-9d13-45fe-89fe-3ba07140ad8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.body.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vidole_sikio_meno"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.body.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480794844","data":{"timestamp":" 947480794844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8a1d9992-9d13-45fe-89fe-3ba07140ad8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.body.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mguu_tumbo_vidole"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.body.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480801469","data":{"timestamp":" 947480801469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8a1d9992-9d13-45fe-89fe-3ba07140ad8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.body.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tumbo_jicho_bega"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.body.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947480813527","data":{"timestamp":" 947480813527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_074611"," gameId":" 8a1d9992-9d13-45fe-89fe-3ba07140ad8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.body.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_tumbo_jicho_bega"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}